{
    "subject": "resource/Thunderbird_Films",
    "predicate": "property/locationCity",
    "object": "resource/Vancouver",
    "human_readable": "Thunderbird Films is located in Vancouver.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8824675679206848,
            "question": "Where is Thunderbird Films located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8686965107917786,
            "question": "In which Canadian city is Thunderbird Films situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5755648612976074,
            "question": "Is Thunderbird Films based in a coastal city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5383545756340027,
            "question": "What city is home to Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45059481263160706,
            "question": "Does Thunderbird Films operate internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43978002667427063,
            "question": "What are some notable productions by Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4357259273529053,
            "question": "What is the history of Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30051061511039734,
            "question": "What type of business is Thunderbird Films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24897301197052002,
            "question": "Are there other film production companies in Vancouver?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19360457360744476,
            "question": "Has Thunderbird Films won any awards for its work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Thunderbird Films is located in Vancouver.",
            "html": "dbpedia_316_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other film production companies in Vancouver?",
            "html": "dbpedia_316_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business is Thunderbird Films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_316_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Thunderbird Films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_316_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_316_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Thunderbird Entertainment Group, of which Thunderbird Films is a part, has its headquarters and offices in Vancouver, among other locations. Therefore, the statement that Thunderbird Films is located in Vancouver is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}